[

](https://classiccountrymusic.com/)

*  

[

](https://classiccountrymusic.com/)

Main Menu

### Artists - A-H

Main Menu

### Artists - I-P

Main Menu

### Artists - Q-Z

Main Menu

### Genres

### A-H

### I-P

### Q-Z

### Traditional

### Bluegrass

### Outlaw

Privacy Policy
==============

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to www.classiccountrymusic.com, and The Real Market Investors Inc. and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to The Real Market Investors Inc. include www.classiccountrymusic.com and Classic Country Music. The Classic Country Music website is a news & entertainment site. By using the Classic Country Music website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

Collection of your Personal Information
=======================================

In order to better provide you with products and services offered, Classic Country Music may collect personally identifiable information, such as your:

* First and Last Name
* Mailing Address
* E-mail Address
* Phone Number

If you purchase Classic Country Music’s products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction.

Classic Country Music may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your:

* Age
* Gender

We do not collect any personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. However, you may be required to provide certain personal information to us when you elect to use certain products or services. These may include: (a) registering for an account; (b) entering a sweepstakes or contest sponsored by us or one of our partners; (c) signing up for special offers from selected third parties; (d) sending us an email message; (e) submitting your credit card or other payment information when ordering and purchasing products and services. To wit, we will use your information for, but not limited to, communicating with you in relation to services and/or products you have requested from us. We also may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Use of your Personal Information
================================

Classic Country Music collects and uses your personal information to operate and deliver the services you have requested.

Classic Country Music may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Classic Country Music and its affiliates.

Sharing Information with Third Parties
======================================

Classic Country Music does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

Classic Country Music may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. Classic Country Music may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Classic Country Music, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Classic Country Music may disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Classic Country Music or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Classic Country Music; and/or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Classic Country Music, or the public.

Please note: The California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”) requires businesses to state in their privacy policy whether or not they disclose personal information in exchange for monetary or other valuable consideration. While CCPA only covers California residents, we believe in, and gladly extend those core rights for people to control their data to all of our users, not just those who live in California.

Tracking User Behavior
======================

Classic Country Music may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Classic Country Music, in order to determine what Classic Country Music services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Classic Country Music to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Automatically Collected Information
===================================

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Classic Country Music. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Classic Country Music website.

Use of Cookies
==============

The Classic Country Music website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Classic Country Music pages, or register with Classic Country Music site or services, a cookie helps Classic Country Music to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Classic Country Music website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Classic Country Music features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Classic Country Music services or websites you visit.

Links
=====

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

Security of your Personal Information
=====================================

Classic Country Music secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Classic Country Music uses the following methods for this purpose:

* SSL Protocol

When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

We strive to take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or alteration of your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations inherent to the Internet which are beyond our control; and (b) security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Site cannot be guaranteed.

Right to Deletion
=================

Subject to certain exceptions set out below, on receipt of a verifiable request from you, we will:

* Delete your personal information from our records; and
* Direct any service providers to delete your personal information from their records.

Please note that we may not be able to comply with requests to delete your personal information if it is necessary to:

* Complete the transaction for which the personal information was collected, fulfill the terms of a written warranty or product recall conducted in accordance with federal law, provide a good or service requested by you, or reasonably anticipated within the context of our ongoing business relationship with you, or otherwise perform a contract between you and us;
* Detect security incidents, protect against malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity; or prosecute those responsible for that activity;
* Debug to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality;
* Exercise free speech, ensure the right of another consumer to exercise his or her right of free speech, or exercise another right provided for by law;
* Comply with the California Electronic Communications Privacy Act;
* Engage in public or peer-reviewed scientific, historical, or statistical research in the public interest that adheres to all other applicable ethics and privacy laws, when our deletion of the information is likely to render impossible or seriously impair the achievement of such research, provided we have obtained your informed consent;
* Enable solely internal uses that are reasonably aligned with your expectations based on your relationship with us;
* Comply with an existing legal obligation; or
* Otherwise use your personal information, internally, in a lawful manner that is compatible with the context in which you provided the information.

Children Under Thirteen
=======================

Classic Country Music does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

E-mail Communications
=====================

From time to time, Classic Country Music may contact you via email for the purpose of providing announcements, promotional offers, alerts, confirmations, surveys, and/or other general communication. In order to improve our Services, we may receive a notification when you open an email from Classic Country Music or click on a link therein.

If you would like to stop receiving marketing or promotional communications via email from Classic Country Music, you may opt out of such communications by “replying STOP” or “clicking on the UNSUBSCRIBE button.”.

External Data Storage Sites
===========================

We may store your data on servers provided by third party hosting vendors with whom we have contracted.

GDPR Privacy
============

Legal Basis for Processing Personal Data under GDPR
---------------------------------------------------

We may process Personal Data under the following conditions:

* Consent: You have given your consent for processing Personal Data for one or more specific purposes.
* Performance of a contract: Provision of Personal Data is necessary for the performance of an agreement with you and/or for any pre\*contractual obligations thereof.
* Legal obligations: Processing Personal Data is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which the Company is subject.
* Vital interests: Processing Personal Data is necessary in order to protect your vital interests or of another natural person.

Your Rights under the GDPR
--------------------------

We undertake to respect the confidentiality of your Personal Data and to guarantee you can exercise your rights.

You have the right under this Privacy Policy, and by law if you are within the EU, to:

* Request access to your Personal Data. The right to access, update or delete the information we have on you. Whenever made possible, you can access, update or request deletion of your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to perform these actions yourself, please contact Us to assist you. This also enables you to receive a copy of the Personal Data We hold about You.
* Request correction of the Personal Data that We hold about you. You have the right to to have any incomplete or inaccurate information we hold about you corrected.
* Object to processing of your Personal Data. This right exists where we are relying on a legitimate interest as the legal basis for our processing and there is something about your particular situation, which makes you want to object to our processing of your Personal Data on this ground. You also have the right to object where we are processing your Personal Data for direct marketing purposes.
* Request erasure of your Personal Data. You have the right to ask us to delete or remove Personal Data when there is no good reason for us to continue processing it.
* Request the transfer of your Personal Data. We will provide to you, or to a third-party you have chosen, your Personal Data in a structured, commonly used, machine-readable format. Please note that this right only applies to automated information which you initially provided consent for us to use or where ye used the information to perform a contract with you.
* Withdraw your consent. You have the right to withdraw your consent on using your Personal Data. If you withdraw your consent, we may not be able to provide you with access to certain specific functionalities of the Service.

Changes to this Statement
=========================

Classic Country Music reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account, by placing a prominent notice on our website, and/or by updating any privacy information. Your continued use of the website and/or Services available after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by that Policy.

Advertising
===========

This Site is affiliated with CMI Marketing, Inc., d/b/a Raptive (“Raptive”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site, and CafeMedia will collect and use certain data for advertising purposes. To learn more about CafeMedia’s data usage, click here: [https://www.cafemedia.com/publisher-advertising-privacy-policy](https://www.cafemedia.com/publisher-advertising-privacy-policy)

We use Google Analytics to analyze the use of our website. Google Analytics gathers information about website use by means of cookies. The information gathered relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of our website. Google’s privacy policy is available at: [https://policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy)

Contact Information
===================

Classic Country Music welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Classic Country Music has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Classic Country Music at:

The Real Market Investors Inc.  
1012 Norman Harris Rd.  
Ashland City, Tennessee 37015

Email Address:  
[\[email protected\]](https://classiccountrymusic.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Telephone number:  
\[949\] 292.8401

Effective as of September 01, 2022

[

](https://classiccountrymusic.com/)

###### A-H

###### I-P

###### Q-Z

###### Genres

* * *

© 2024 Classic Country Music | Legendary Stories and Songs
